{
    "id": "bfdaf8d910744969919fd80f757e2e53",
    "title": "Simple Past Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. her fiancé at a library.",
            "description": "Met is the past simple form of meet.",
            "answers": [
                "meet",
                "meeted",
                "met"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………….. some apples yesterday.",
            "description": "Bought is the past simple form of buy.",
            "answers": [
                "buyed",
                "bought",
                "buy"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………….. to remain a spinster.",
            "description": "Chose is the past simple form of choose. ",
            "answers": [
                "choose",
                "choosed",
                "chose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat ……………………… out of the window.",
            "description": "Ran is the past simple form of run.",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "runned",
                "ran"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… a terrible experience yesterday.",
            "description": "Had is the past simple form of have. ",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "have had",
                "had had"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………….. across the river.",
            "description": "Swam is the past simple form of swim. ",
            "answers": [
                "swam",
                "swimmed",
                "swamed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… around but I ……………………… anyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "turn, didn't saw",
                "turned, didn't see",
                "turned, didn't saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. in a low voice.",
            "description": "Spoke is the past simple form of speak.",
            "answers": [
                "speaked",
                "spoke",
                "spoked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… the vase accidentally.",
            "description": "Broke is the past simple form of break.",
            "answers": [
                "breaked",
                "brock",
                "broke"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The bird ………………………… away.",
            "description": "Flew is the past simple form of fly. ",
            "answers": [
                "flied",
                "flew",
                "flyed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… the vegetables with a knife.",
            "description": "Cut is the past and past participle form of cut. ",
            "answers": [
                "cut",
                "cutted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………. the candle out.",
            "description": "Blew is the past simple form of blow. ",
            "answers": [
                "blowed",
                "blew",
                "blewed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}